# Ivan Dimitrov

#### ABOUT

I am a backend software developer who enjoys working in a high energy environment using modern technologies. I am used to applying agile methodologies, breaking down user requirements into tasks, teaching junior developers. Some of the technologies used daily are GOlang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL and RESTFul services. I am familiar with git, docker, LaTeX and NoSQL databases as well. I am not afraid of making decisions and taking responsibility. I have also experience with enterprise projects using Java and Android.

## Professional EXPERIENCE

### StageAI, Sofia

Senior Software Developer

May 2020 - Present

- ▷ Solving complex tasks mainly using GOlang and PostgreSQL.
- ▶ Breakdown tasks and requirements.
- ▶ Helping and teaching juniors colleagues.
- ▶ Supervise the working processes applying agile methodologies.

Software Developer

Jan 2018 - May 2020

- Developed various web application using mainly with Golang, SQL and NoSQL DBs, REST and Graphql.
- ▶ Deliver high quality code.

#### Musala Soft, Sofia

Software developer

Aug 2016 - Dec 2017

▶ Worked as a contractor for Experian maintaining their existing project using mainly internal tools in the Java ecosystem.

Junoir Software Developer

Aug 2015 - Aug 2016

- ▶ Developed native android applications with Java.
- ▶ Maintained Java enterpise application using JSP, maven, OracleDB.
- ▶ Maintained hybrid mobile application with Javascript and apache Cordova.

# Game developer-intern, Varna

Software Developer

Aug 2014 - Sept 2014

#### SKILLS

Golang, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, RESTFul services.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Technical University, Varna

M.S of Computer Science Sep 2013 – June 2015 B.S of Electronics Sep 2009 - June 2013

#### CERTIFICATIONS Oracle Certified Professional, Oracle

Sep 2017

Agile Software Development, The Business Institute

Apr 2017

Managing Team Performance, The Business Institute

Feb 2017

Oracle Certified Associate, Oracle

Nov 2016